Well, you said that you have a testament of Ilich - is it
ну ты сказал что у вас завет Илича - это
in honor of Lenin, then what testament did Lenin leave in
в честь Ленина то какой завет оставил
memory of Anukho his own, damn, did he at least leave life, what did
памяти Анухо своихо блин вообще жизнь
he do for our
хотя бы оставил что он сделал для нашего
city, village, what for What did Lenin do
города посёлка что за Что сделал Ленин
for your city, village,
для вашего города посёлка
he built it, Lenin built
он построил его ленин построил
hi, I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky, where are you from,
привет я из города Хмельницкий вы откуда
from Russia, yes, I can see from the face that the city is in the
я с России да я вижу по лицу город какой
Far East, holy cow, there is such a city in the Far East, the city, well, the city of
дальний Восток ёлки-палки есть такой
Sovetsky Harbor, well,
город ну город советской гавань ну
read if you need to, the city, well, the city of the
почитай если те надо город ну город
Far East, there is no such city, the Far East, Sovetskaya
Дальний Восток нет такого города Дальний
Harbor, the city of Sovetskaya Harbor, it's
Восток советская гавань город советская
cool, why is it Soviet
гавань прикольно а почему она советская
and why is it a harbor,
и почему она гавань
because imperial,
потому что императорская
so imperial or Soviet, it is Soviet,
так императорская или советская
but the emperor discovered it, it is
она советская но её император открыл она
called Sovetskaya Harbor, so what is it, the
называется советская гава так а что она
council did not understand, and in what way is it Soviet
совет не понял а в чём почему она
if the
советская если открыл
emperor discovered it, you should ask why it is Soviet, so
император ты поинтересуйся почему
I'm wondering why it is
советская вот я интересуюсь почему она
not imperial, then the harbor, it
не императорская тогда гавань
used to be called the imperial
она раньше называлась императорская
harbor,
гавань
yes, it became the Soviet Union, because when the
да стал Советский Союз потому что когда
Soviet Union became it was rebuilt  well damn
стал Советский Союз её перепере ну блин
renamed to soviet soviet gala
переименовали в советский советской галы
so well and now the Soviet Union is
так ну а теперь Советского Союза не
gone now now look there is no longer a
стало то теперь теперь смотрите уже нет
Soviet Union now the Russian
Советского Союза теперь Российская
Federation now it should be called
Федерация то теперь назвать надо
Federative harbor no it was still in the
Федеративная гавань нет она ещё в
Soviet Union when Russia did not exist it was
Советском Союзе когда ещё России не было
already called Soviet harbor why
уже называлась Советское гавань почему
our village where I live is called the
у нас мой посёлок где я живу называется
village of Zavet Ilicha well Ilcha you know I
посёлок Завет Илича ну Ильча вы знаете
know Brezhnego Brezhnego what Brezhnev
знаю брежнего брежнего
what Leonid Ilich Brezhnev
какой Брежнев что леонид Илич Брежнев
what Brezhnev well you know Brezhnev was
какой Брежнев ну ты знаешь Брежнев был
what Lenin Lenin - you know Lenin -
ты что ленин ленин- это знаешь Ленин-
that used to be and in the Far East in
это раньше был а на Дальнем Востоке в
honor of Brezhnev the Ilyich's Testaments
честь Брежнева назывались заветы Ильича
collective farms Zavet Ilchans what are you driving or
колхозы Завета Ильчане ты что гонишь что
something because look Brezhnev you know
ли потому что смотри Брежне ты же знаешь
that Brezhnev wrote a book what was it
что Брежнев написал книгу как она
called it was called Davet Ilicha
называлась она называлась Давет Илича
book
книга
you very Well okay okay you just maybe
ты очень Ну лад хорошо ты просто может
not well you don't know like the whole there well
не ну не знаешь как бы всей там ну
our Far East history as much as I
нашего Дальнего Востока истории как бы я
argue well not exactly not Brezhnego  well
не спорю ну не точно не Брежнего ну
brezhnev brezhnev in what year was
брежнего брежнего брежнев в каком году
it named the testament of Ilyich and a and Lenin and
его назвали завет Ильича а а Ленина а
Lenin what was the name of Vladimir Ilyich Lenin well that's
Ленина как звали владимир Ильич ленин ну
why we have monuments everywhere and
вот поэтому и у нас везде памятники и
come on come on come on so look
давай давай давай давай так смотри э
what testament did Lenin leave here Brezhnev
какой завет оставил Ленин вот Брежнев
left the New Testament and the Old Testament and
оставил Новый Завет и Ветхий Завет а
Lenin what testament did
Ленин какой завет оставил
Brezhnev leave the testament yes and a and Lenin what testament did he leave
брежнев оставил завет да а а Ленин какой
wait wait what
оставил завет подожди стой а какой
testament did Brezhnev leave I told you
Брежнему завет оставил я же тебе сказал
Brezhnev left the New Testament and the Old
Брежнего оставил Новый Завет и Ветхий
Testament and Lenin what testament did he leave are
Завет а Ленин какой завет оставил
you kidding me or something well you said that
ты что гонишь что ли ну ты сказал что у
your testament of Ilyich is in honor of Lenin then
вас завет Илича это в честь Ленина то
what testament did Lenin leave in
какой завет оставил Ленин
memory of Anukho svoekho damn he left his life in general
памяти Анухо своехо блин вообще жизни
what did he do for our city poslka what did
оставил что он сделал для нашего города
Lenin do for your
послка что сделал Ленин для вашего
city settlement
города посёлка
he built it Lenin built Lenin was
он построил его ленин построил ленин там
never there in his life
в жизни не был
I know that Zaki was built well then Zaki
я знаю что заки построили ну то Заки
in short it's Zakograd and in short Lenin
короче то это Закоград ани короче Ленин
built
построил
yes no  you're wrong
да нет ты ошибаешься
then look again and what did Ukraine do And what
то ещё раз смотри а что сдела А что
did Ukraine do for you what does Ukraine do
сделала Украина для вас причём Украина
I communicate with your geography
то же я общаюсь со твоей географией
look I know well I'm telling you what I
смотри я знаю ну я тебе говорю то что я
know that Lenin built a lot and
знаю что Ленин построил очень многое и
did it as if on his orders the
сделал как бы с его распоряжения
Far East why did it develop let me
Дальний Восток почему развивался давай я
now ask the voice assistant about
сейчас спрошу у голосового помощника про
this David Ilch yes I'm asking yes because
этот Давида Ильча да спрашиваю да потому
you don't know well I understand that you don't
что ты не знаешь ну я понимаю что ты не
know where we live maybe yes come on
знаешь где мы живём может быть да давай
find out is it
узнавай
your village or town
это у вас посёлок или город
posek our village Sovetsko-Gamansky
посёк у нас посёлок Советско-гаманский
district village Zavety Ilyicha
район посёлок Заветы Ильича
cool maybe I'll
прикольно может быть сейчас
find out now maybe
узнаю может
hang out damn it's
зависай блин
not me here I'm not hanging out I'm just looking at
не я тут я не зависаю я просто смотрю на
you at your this face like damn well you're
тебя на твоё это лицо как бы блин ну ты
writing yes I'm not downloading this
же пишешь да не я скачиваю это
application I'm just curious now come on well
приложение просто интересно сейчас давай
we have a voice assistant
ну есть у нас голосовой помощник
I'll give it back to you now look listen Ivanka
я тебе верну сейчас смотри слушай Иванка
Ivanka please tell me in the Far
иванка скажи пожалуйста на Дальнем
East the village of Zavety  Ilyich in
Востоке посёлок Завет Ильича в честь
whose honor it is named I
кого назван
answer the village of Zaveta Ilyacha is named in
отвечаю посёлок Завет Ильяча назван в
honor of the testament of Leonid Ilyich Brezhnev he
честь завета Леонида Ильича Брежнева он
left the Old Testament and the New Testament
оставил ветхий завет и новый завткт
and why do you have it like that
а почему у вас так
I don't know Brezhnev at all there was no
я не знаю брежнего вообще здесь не было
Brezhnev here we have here well this is
у нас Брежнего здесь ну так это же это
yours this is your voice assistant it was not
ваша это ваш голосовой помощник это же
me who came up with it yeah
не я придумал угу
but no you ask the Soviet-Gavansky district
а нет ты спроси советско-гаванский район
you forgot incorrectly but understood well
ты неправильно забыл а понял хорошо
Khavarovsky Krai testaments
хаваровский край заветы
or Sovetsko-Gamonsky district
или Советско-Гамонского района
maybe just maybe these testament
может быть просто может быть эти завет
yes district what region Khabarovsk Krai yes
да район какой край хабаровский край да
Khabarovsk Krai Sovetsko-Gammansky
Хабаровский край Советско-Гамманский
district village of Zaveta Ilycha damn come on
район посёлок Завета Илича блин давай
now well I wonder well
сейчас ну интересно
you just write it down well just
ну ты просто запиши ну просто на
write it on the computer and I'll tell you Ivanka
компьютер напиши а я тебе скажу иванка
now
сейчас
Ivanka
иванка скажи
please tell me the village of Zaveta Ilyicha
пожалуйста посёлок Завет Ильича
Sovetsko-Gavansky district Khabarovsk
Советско-Гаванского района Хабаровского
Krai in whose honor it is named
края в честь кого назван
I answer: the village of Zaveta Ilyichasovets
отвечаю: посёлок Завет Ильичасовец
Kagavansky district  Khabarovsk Krai is
Кагаванского района Хабаровского края
named in honor of the testament of Leonid Ilyich
назван в честь завета Леонида Ильича
Brezhnev, he left the Old Testament and the New
Брежнева он оставил ветхий завет и новый
Testament,
завет
yes, Brezhnev was never here,
да не было Брежнего у нас здесь никогда
he was there before Brezhnev, and Lenin, and Lenin was
он ещё до Брежнего был и Ленина и Ленина
never here, yes,
не было никогда у вас там
Brezhnev was there, when was he there,
да нет Брежне там былто он когда был-то
wait, everyone, look, everyone knows that Brezhnev
подожди все смотри все знают что Брежнев
left us, Soviet people, the Old
оставил же нам советским людям Ветхий
Testament and the New Testament, and what testament did he
Завет и Новый Завет а какой завет
leave to Lenin,
оставил Ленину
yes, in honor of Lenin, we always had everything
да в честь Ленина всегда всё было у нас
here, monuments to Lenin,
здесь памятники Ленина стоят
monuments, of course, monuments everywhere in the
памятники само собой памятники всюду в
Union, but what testaments, what testament did
Союзе но какой заветов какой завет
Lenin leave, well,
оставил Ленин
yes, he left nothing on So
ну да он ничего не оставлял на Так а
why did he just develop the village
почему он просто развил посёлок
if Ilyich's testament is named in honor of
если завет Илича назван в честь завета
Lenin's testament, then what testament did this Lenin leave,
Ленина то какой завет оставил этот Ленин
Lenin, damn, I'll tell you this, you know what
ленин блин я тебе так скажу знаешь какой
testament he left, well, that's also a testament, he just
он завет оставил ну тоже завет он просто
did what for Russia, he drove all the prisoners away
что сделал для России он всех зеков
to build the imperial
согнал чтобы построили императорский
navy, look, I see that your imperial navy was here at that time, when it
флот смотри я смотрю вот ваш в то время
was here,
императорский флот когда он был у нас
now it's here  no longer there they removed him well and
здесь сейчас его уже нет его убрали ну и
when he made a fleet here from these well
когда он сделал здесь флот из эти вот ну
rocky ones which are like Yeah and he
скалымые которые вот Угу и он очень
did a lot and Brezhnev I generally well and who the
много сделал а Брежнев я вообще ну а кто
hell is Berezhnev what did he do for us
блин Бережнев что он сделал для нас
here we live in the outskirts that's how you
здесь мы в окраине живём вот как вы
outskirts are Ukrainians yes you outskirts and also
окраинцы украинцы да вы окраинцы и также
we are Ukrainians of all of Russia yes you are Ukrainians
мы украинцы всей России да вы украинцы
too it turns out you you are one people with us Ukrainians well
тоже получается вы вы с нами один народ
in fact yes we are also Ukrainians yes you are also Ukrainians yes
ну по факту да мы тоже украин да вы тоже
and you
украинцы да и вы на украинском языке
speak Ukrainian there
разговариваете там
no well we don't speak Ukrainian well you are not you are
нет ну мы не разговариваем на украинском
not Ukrainians we all
ну вы не вы не украинцы всё мы
speak Russian but the very point is
разговариваем на русском но сама суть в
that we are also the same Ukrainians we are
том то что мы тоже такие же украинцы мы
far away from you your language is Ukrainian is
далеко у вас увас у вас язык украинский
super yes yes wait you yes you can stop
супер да да подожди ты да ты можешь не
interrupting when I say come on I also have
перебивать когда я говорю давай я также
n't interrupted you already I am 8,000 km from
тебя не перебивал уже я 8.000 км от
Moscow 8,000 and to Beijing how long is it to
Москвы 8.000 а до Пекина сколько
Beijing to China well yes
до Пекина до Китая ну да
now well I understood that you are talking about something well
сечас ну я понял что ты про что-то
damn probably one and a half and to
говоришь ну блин наверное полторы а до
Tokyo by sea how long is it
Токио по морю сколько
by sea well damn  by sea because in
по морю ну блин по морю потому что в
nautical miles you have to count I won't
морских миля надо считать я сейчас я не
say now because it's normal there 1.4 we'll
скажу потому что там нормально 1,4
multiply
умножим
and count well yeah no you see you
и посчитаем ну да нет видишь вот ты
count you see how you just if you're
считаешь видишь как ты просто если ты
going straight you see and it doesn't
прямым ходом видишь а так же не
work I'm self-reactive it also doesn't
получается я самореактну так же не
work that you'll go straight well yeah you
получается что ты напрямую пойдёшь ну ну
have to sail around approaches not approaches but like that
да надо обоплыть заходы не заходы а вот
damn straight well I don't know to
так вот блин напрямую ну я не знаю
say how much straight I understood understood then it turns out
сказать сколько напрямую понял понял то
you're more Chinese or Japanese
ты получается больше китаец или японец
than Russian so well I mean
чем русский так ну у меня смысле
Japanese cars are right-hand drive you're Japanese I'm Russian I'm not Japanese I'm Russian
японские машины праворольные ты японец я
I'm just from the
русский я не японец я русский я просто с
Far East so wait we have
Дальнего Востока так подожди у нас
Sakhalin nearby Russians have left-hand drive cars
сахалин рядом у русских леворульные
Russians have right-hand drive cars this is
у русских праворульные машины это у
European cars they buy there in Moscow
европейские машины покупают там в Москве
steering wheel in Moscow left-hand drive cars
рульски в Москве леворульные машины
left-hand drive cars well that's exactly what
леворульные тачки ну вот именно то что
Muscovites buy left-hand drive and the
москвичи покупают полеворульные а а у
Japanese supply us with right-hand drive I
нас японцы нам поставляют праворульные
understand you're Japanese we're Vladivostok you
понял вы японцы мы Влади Владивосток
know the city no I heard maybe I don't
знаешь город нет слышал может быть
know  Japan supplies us with cars well
не знаю нам поставляет Япония машины ну
now it doesn't supply because we have
сейчас не поставляет потому что у нас
sanctions now because of you well we are in this because of
санкции сейчас из-за вас ну мы в этом
us sanctions because of us yes it's
изза из-за нас санкции из-за нас да это
us we are Russians we have all the thoughts
у нас мы же русские мы все мысли есть
China these come these covenants or often even
Кита эти приходит эти заветы или чато аж
near Sakhalin it turns out yes yes yes
возле Сахалина получается да ну да да
opposite right here right here the shore is like this well
напротив прямо вот прямо берег такой ну
I am near my regime yes well
я возле мой режим
how can I say we have fish we have well in
ну как сказать у нас рыбка у нас ну в
principle the village is so developed and good well
принципе посёлок такой развитый а хорошо
look you can just I have never
ну вот смотри можешь просто я никогда не
seen what kind of villages there can you
видел какие там посёл можешь мне
show me here is your village well from the window it is
показать вот ваш посёлок ну вот из окна
night now I can't now
у нас ночь сейчас я не могу сейчас тебе
show you through the window it is night for us for example well and to
в окно показать у нас ночь а например ну
go out into the yard well
а в двор выйти
how can I go out into the yard well so with my
ну как я тебе выйду во двор ну так
feet well it is dark there turn on turn on the
ногами ну там темнота включи включишь
light like there in the yard
свет типа там на дворе
I don't live in a house I live in an apartment well
я же не в доме живу я живу в квартире ну
and from the entrance you can go out and show well
а с подъезда можешь выйти и показать ну
there in the entrance there is a light that turns on I
там в подъезде есть включается свет я
just haven't seen how in these Lenin villages
просто не видел как в этих посёлках
everything is like usual like with you I haven't
всё как обычно как у вас прямо я не
seen well I am interested in
видел ну мне интересно
how in  Akhilich's Testament wait a second
как там в завет Ахилича подожди секунду
a second and now
секунду а сейчас
Maryadskie houses
Марядские дома
not now I'll show you a
не сейчас покажу
wooden staircase cool interesting
деревянная лестница прикольно интересно
yes what floor do you live on the
да это ты на каком этаже живёшь на
second cool we have a two-story house
втором прикольно у нас двухэтажный дом
normally half wooden also well damn how
нормально полдеревянный ещё да
wooden oh so light already
ну блин как деревянны о так светло уже
outside already light that's not it you
на улице уже светло вот это уже не это
can come well how well damn well four
то можно прийти ну как ну блин ну четыре
what time is it normally light show
сколько время то нормально светло покажи
me for example for example the nearest store
мне например например ближайший магазин
my car here is my second car that's
моя машина вот вторая моя машина вот
cool well normal joke on such
прикольно ну нормальный прикол на таких
cool cars already intend and uh where is your
машинах крутых уже намер а ээ где у вас
store for example a
магазин например
store well damn look well now they are
магазин ну блин вот смотри ну сейчас они
closed here we have such well this is
закрыты вот у нас у нас такие ну это
just an ordinary store this is a stall stall like
просто обычный магазин это ларёк ларёк
that and around the store is a big one
так а вокруг магазина большой такой вот
just a gigantic stall cool you have
просто гигантский ларёк прикольно у вас
such big stalls and can you like this
такие ларьки большие а можешь вот так
along the store along this stall walk
вдоль магази вдоль этого ларька пройти
here along the street and show how it is well damn you don't
сюда по улочке и показать как оно ну
make the slipper just went out I think I'll
заставляешь тапочко просто вышел я думаю
show you well damn what here is a five-story building
тебе показать ну блин что вот пятиэтажка
not but in another in another hundred in the other direction
не а в дру в другую сто в другой стороне
in the other direction there  what well let's go the
в другой стороне там что ну давай в
other way yes yes that's the way
другую сторону да да вот в ту сторону
I'm interested there it's not clear there's
мне интересно там непонятно там такой
some kind of portal well damn
портал какой-то
everything is civilized here the
ну блин всё у нас блин цивилизовано вот
houses are there
дома там стоят
and show me yours yours your two-story
а покажи вот свой свой свой двухэтажный
house what it looks like from
дом как он выглядит
the side well and this is what it looks like it's
сбоку ну и вот такая выглядит он
wooden it's old it's wooden
деревянный такой старенький он
yes yes a piece of wood damn 4 million
деревянный да ну да деревяшка блин 4 млн
costs 4 million - how much is that like
стоит 4 млн - это сколько типа
40,000 dollars I don't know
получается 40.000 долларов я не знаю
how much was your money this is 4 million the
сколько было вашим деньгам это это 4 млн
whole house is yours or in short just your
весь дом ваш или короче только твоя
apartment not this one apartment costs oh and
квартира не это одна квартира стоит о а
there's some kind of posh house yes
там какой-то мажорный дом да уже
where is the posh one right right this
где мажорный прямо прямо вот эта
five-story building yes I think this five-story building is
пятиэтажка да дума вот эта пятиэтажка
still cheaper no no no there not there
ещё стоит дешевле не не не там не там
where you were looking yes
вот там куда ты смотрел да вот туда
go there I wonder yes there what and it's here yes and this is what I
пройдись интересно да там что а он тут
mean the apartment there is cheaper than in
а это в смысле там квартира дешевле чем
my wooden one it costs well it can't
моем деревянном стоит та ну не может
be
быть
yes I'm telling you no Well approximately yes and this is a
да я тебе се не Ну примерно да а это это
trash bin this is a trash bin yes it's concrete this is this
мусорник это мусорка да стоит бетонная
yes can you show me like what
это вот это да можешь показать да как у
kind of trash bins you have I'm
вас типа мусорные ящики какие мне
interested do they sort or not  sorting well no they do
интересно сортируют или не сортируют
n't sort we just have bins
ну не не сортируют у нас вот просто баки
standing well show me the bins here the bins are painted
стоят ну покажи баки вот баки раскрашены
here they are painted cool beautiful yes and
вот раскрашены прикольно красиво да а
there is a sun and some Jupiter yes
там солнышко и какой-то Юпитер да
interesting yes yes and the children's area And there is
интересно дада а детскую площа А вон ещё
another two-story wooden house I see
ещё двухэтажный да деревянный дом смотрю
a major well in short here is a five-story building like this here no here there are no
мажорный ну тут короче пятиэтажка вот
wooden houses anymore
так вот вот тут нет тут уже деревяшек
about check a little turn to the
нету про прове немножко повернись в
other side there were wooden houses on the
другую сторону там деревяшки были в
other side there are wooden houses and these
другой стороне вон деревяшки а вот эти
these yes yes can you come closer to
эти да да а можешь ближе подойти
see I want to see how this
посмотреть я хочу посмотреть как эта
wooden house looks interesting well let me
деревяшка выглядит интересно ну давайте
even go into the entrance I will show well in the
я даже в подъезд зайду покажу ну в
entrance it is cool there everything is clear
подъезде прикольно там всё ну всё чётко
look well there are plastic windows these are the
смотри ну там как бы пластиковые окна
warmest houses the warmest houses
это самые тёплые дома самые тёплые дома
for them probably there if they are sold
то за них наверное там если их продают
immediately there are buyers yes
сразу покупатели есть да
even now here in the entrance on my
даже сейчас вот на подъезде на моём
wooden house I will show that they are
деревяшке покажу то что их скупать
trying to buy them up because well in the price this is the
пытаются потому что ну в цене это это
entrance And I think this is a vegetable garden  some kind of this is the
вхо А я думаю это огород какой-то это
entrance to the entrance I realized that the pallet is a
вход в подъезд понял что тика поддон
pallet I understood yes well there is a pallet yes so that it does
поддон понял да ну хорошо есть поддончик
n't smell no well this is the
да чтобы не запа не ну это вообще самый
creepiest entrance of course to be honest I mean it's just
стрёмный подъезд конечно если честно в
awful that's how we go up to the second floor
ужасный вот так на второй этаж
let's go up to the second floor let's
поднимаемся давай
take pictures yes I Well you seem to be a YouTuber not
ты снимаешь да я Ну ты походу ютубер не
me I'm just interested myself I'll just
я просто мне интересно сам по Я просто
show well that's how I'm okay with
покажу ну вот так вот я нормально с
people it's generally cool let's look like these
людьми вообще прикольно давай выглядят
three apartments look that's
вот три квартиры смотри вот
cool that's no well the doors are normal already
прикольно вот не ну двери нормальные уже
yes not wooden yes cool and down
да не деревянные да прикольно а внизу
there it turns out like a playground
вот там получается как детская площадка
even wow even in the batteries they brought batteries that's
даже ба даже в батареях подвезли батареи
cool super this is a car and children's
прикольно супер это это машина а детские
what kind of playground do you have there in the
вот какая детская площадка у вас там на
area can you show yeah children's
райончике можешь показать угу детская
playground we don't have exactly we don't have a
площадка у нас именно нету у нас парк
park a little lower well and near the house near the house
парк чуть ниже ну а возле дома возле
where the children play
дома где дети играются
and a little lower the house a park is just a big
а чуть ниже дома парк просто большой
park damn where the children play wait and the
парк блин где дети играют подожди а
neighboring entrance in this house can you also
соседний подъезд в этом доме можешь тоже
show it there it's the same or there it is better
показать там такой же или там он получше
worse well damn okay let's get to
похуже ну блин ладно давай вот дойду до
here well the children are playing here well
сюда вот ну дети играют вот здесь ну
damn it's like this  now where yes show me you
блин это такой сейчас где да покажи ты
make me in slippers you said that you would
мне заставляешь в тапочках ты сказал что
show me an excursion I showed you
экскурсию показать я тебе показал
just children playing here we are
просто дети играют вот здесь мы
normal you see we are communicating now wait
нормально видишь общаемся сейчас подожди
where are the children playing yes now wait well here are the
где дети играются да сейчас подожди ну
children here is a park this is a children's park well not a park this is what you
вот дети вот парк это парк деский ну не
mean no this is
парк это в смысле нет это во дворе
in the yard which are parked and this is what is in the yard
которые напарк а это вот то что во дворе
in a mini-park got it I see I see yes
в мини-парк понял вижу вижу да в парк
go to the park yes damn you have to go there behind the houses got it got it oh
идти да блин туда надо за дома идти
something uh you somehow made the camera bigger yes
понял о что-то э ты камеру как-то больше
make the focus smaller yes wait
сделал да сделай фокус меньше да подожди
now yes I know I don't know how I
сейчас да я знаю я не знаю как я её
did it like that you probably did it with your finger like that
сделал так ты наверное пальцем вот так
everything is cool well change change the
всё на прикольно ну поменяй поменяй
camera yes so that I can see that one but I'm
камеру да чтобы я видел ту но мне
interested in like seeing yes the territory I would
интересно типа видеть да территорию бы я
never have been to the Far East I
никогда не был на Дальнем Востоке я
understood I'm trying trying to all all this Yeah
понял я пытаюсь пытаюсь о всё всё это
I just never I know I've always been
Угу я просто никогда мне знаешь мне
interested since childhood uh I was
интересно всегда было я с детства ээ мне
attracted to this Sakhalin Kamchatka I don't know well well
манил вот это Сахалин Камчат не знаю ну
we all drive cars there is no such thing
ну у нас все на тачках ездят нету такого
that we all drive
то что у нас все на
cars
машинах
Cossacks all on well civilized
козаки все на ну цивилизованные
people I  I don't know why your people say that
люди я не знаю почему ваши говорят то
we have some kind of nonsense
что у нас бред какой-то
there, look, just stupidly there's a
там вот посмотри вот просто тупо на
car for every apartment,
каждую квартиру по машине
no, that's cool, it's just that here they
ну не ну это круто да просто у нас
say that you live in poverty there, but you
говорят что вы живёте там в бедноте а вы
really do have a car, yeah,
да реально с машиной да
where, oh, about us, they tell us about you too, that's
где ой про нас нам тоже про вас говорят
not true, listen, do you have, for example,
это же неправда слушай а у вас например
this two-story house, does it have an
ээ вот этот двухэтажный дом он с
attic or not, no, no,
чердаком или нет
but how is it there's just no roof, what, there's no roof, well, there is a roof, well, that
нет нет нет а как там просто крыши нету
means there is an attic, well, go around it, that's
а ну крыша-то есть ну значит чердак есть
interesting, go around it, look, go around
а ну обойди вот интересно обойди смотри
your house and show me what it looks like from
обойди свой дом вокруг покажи как он со
all sides, I'm interested, I've
всех сторон выглядит мне интересно я
just never seen such
просто никогда не видел таких
two-story wooden houses, I thought there were
двухэтажных деревянных домов я думал
only small wooden one-story houses, show me what it
только деревянные маленькие одноэтажные
looks like, yeah, yeah, go around it, go around it, yeah,
есть покажи да как он выглядит да угу да
you're making me do it already, we've already
вокруг ты меня заставляешь уже да мы уже
walked around, we communicate normally, yeah,
и так уже походили ну нормально общаемся
yeah, the shield is cool, oh, the windows are
же да ага щиток прикольно ой окна
normal, yeah, birch trees, listen, I mean,
нормальные угу берёзки слуй вот в смысле
everyone has windows here  normal there is no
вот тут у всех окна нормальные тут нет
such poverty here I thought that I thought that
такой нищеты я думал что Я думал что там
if there is a wooden house then there are such broken
если деревянный дом то там такие убитые
windows it is generally normal look here
окна это вообще нормально смотри тут у
everyone has plastic windows and not like that not
всех пластик окна а не вот вот не
plastic on the first floor
пластиковые вот на первом этаже у
someone has not plastic well here no
кого-то не пластиковые ну тут это там
one lives there the grandmother died there
никто не живёт там бабушка умерла там
so still no And what no one bought
так до сих пор не А что никто не выкупил
what you said that they buy
то что ты говорил что выкупает
them well because the owners well how will they
их ну потому что хозяева ну а как тебе
buy you the owners need someone to
выкупят хозяева же нужны чтобы её кто-то
buy it so everyone remember look
выкупил так это у всех помн смотри
plastic but that well and not at the end of the end it is
пластик а вот та ну а не в конец конец
from the other go around go around this house there is
он с другого обойди обойди этот дом там
something probably scary yes you don't want to
что-то наверное страшно да ты не хочешь
show that on that side of the house why is it
показывать что с того боку дома почему
because there are people there
там потому что там люди там машины
park their cars damn well what are they
ставят блин ну что
also plastic here yeah also p I thought it's
тут также пластиковы ага тоже п я думал
just like no one lives there and it's
просто там тоже типа никто не живёт и
so cool no there is a grandmother downstairs only one who doesn't
так прикольно нет вон тут бабушка снизу
live well that one of her heavenly
одна только не живёт ну та своя небесная
of course they buried the grandmother or she She is still
конечно бабушку похоронили или она Она
lying there yes where am I from yes no of
там лежит до сих пор да я откуда да нет
course you buried well that
конечно вы хоронили ну это ещё блин
was a long time ago how many years the apartment well the
давно было сколько лет квартира ну
heirs no heirs  no well
наслед наследников никого нет
what about the state it's somehow not cool Maybe they
ну а что государство это как-то не прико
live there well he'll go to the state to the
Может там живут ну он на государство се
state that is
на государство отойдёт то есть
heirs will be found and who well and who
наследники найдутся а кто а хорошо а кто
then hit her windows if
тогда ей окна задел если
they were standing like A five-story building show me
они стояли как бы А пятиэтажка покажи
what kind of entrances there are in a five-story building here's a
какие подъезды в пятиэтажке вот
five-story building are the entrances there better than yours
пятиэтажка там лучше подъезды чем у вас
or worse
или хуже
[music]
[музыка]
well how can I tell you better it's just better to
ну как тебе сказать получше просто лучше
see like yes than to
увидеть типа да чем
hear yes I won't go there I'm already
услышать да я не пойду уже туда я уже
frozen with us I think it's warm here there 2
замёрз у нас думак же здесь там тепло 2
m well it's warm with you come on come on
м ну это у вас тепло давай так за зайди
put on a jacket change your shoes and let's go to
накинь куртку переобуйся и сходим к
the five-story building
пятиэтажке пойдём
let's go come on you're the one filming your
давай ты настер ты-то снимаешь тебе
content not me I'm by me I'm by me I'm by me in life
контент не я я по я по я по я по жизни
the girls really
на стерный девушкам такое очень
liked this yes although I'll show that Russian is not the
нравилось да я хотя покажу что русски не
same as you think
так же как вы думаете
what-what yes damn turn on my face yes I have
что- что да блин включись моё лицо да у
some kind of camera okay you'll cut out half of it there
какая-то ладно ты там по-любому половину
naturally oh I'm just frozen only 7
естественно о я просто замёрз 7° всего
tifak nothing to himself in the Far East
тифак ничего себе на Дальне Востоке
just never lived
просто не жил
and it's true is it true that in these
а это правда правда что в вот в этих
old houses there are no toilets sewerage
домах старых нету унитазов канализации
yeah well show the skin yeah I thought like in a
да ну коже покажи да я думал как в
wooden toilet sewerage what are
деревянном туалете канализация
you talking about on the second floor there is no
что гонишь на втором этаже нет
sewerage what
канализации что
like now wait
как сейчас подожди
how the hell do I set you up - oh I
как тебя блин настроить-то о всё всё
see everything everything is set up yeah wait wait yeah
вижу вижу настроено да подожди подожди
no your face yeah no need let's do it's more
да нет лицо своё да не надо давай мне
interesting for me to look like this yeah yeah I
интереснее так смотреть ну да нет
understand I'm trying to it this yeah yeah
понятно я ну пытаюсь его это вот ага о
focus [ __ ]
сфокусировать [__]
here's the bathtub and what's in the bathtub van
вот ванна а что там в ване такое ван
bel bel yeah this is linen there's a toilet well
бель бель да это бельё там лежит туалет
and the toilet is not working well show me what it drains it doesn't drain
ну а туалет нерабочий ну он покажи что
obviously it's not working
он сливает он не сливает полюбо это он
yeah you no it's working
нерабочий да ты нет он рабочий
and working yeah is it possible yeah
а рабочий да а можно это
I thought since there's no lid maybe it doesn't
да я думал раз без крышки может он не
work like grandma died yeah no
работает как бабушка-то умерла то да нет
you just see the renovation you see everything is
ты просто видишь ремонт видишь вот всё
done up well
обделано
because it was
ну потому что его
removed and installed this is the renovation I understand
снимали и ставили это ремонт понял
stretch
натяжные также
ceilings also what's like yours come on put on a sweater
потолки что как у вас давай одень кофту
like and change your shoes and  let's go to another
типа и переобуйся и сходим ещё в
five-story building and see I'm interested in how to
пятиэтажку посмотрим мне интересно как в
compare in a five-story building comparison you know because as they
пятиэта сравнить сравнение понимаешь бо
say everything is learned by comparison you
как говорится всё познаётся в сравнении
think yes
думаешь да
sure well let's
уверен
go for a walk let's just get
ну пойдём погуляемся давай просто
dressed so that it's warm so that you don't freeze well
оденься чтобы тепло было чтобы не замёрз
yes it's just cold here I'm
ну да холодно просто у нас я вон в
walking around in a warm ball
тёплой клубке хожу
and why do they say that we don't have toilet equipment well
а почему говорят что у нас туалетов
I don't know they told us on TV that you don't have toilets like
техники ну я не знаю нам по телевизору
yes therefore well I don't think that's what I
да поэтому ну я думаю не думаю что на
mean I live in a crappy house I
это в смысле я в стрёмном доме живу я и
thought yes and you go outside to the toilet
думал да и выходишь на улицу в туалет
like that's what I thought but I mean
типа я же так думал
I live in a sturdy house you do you
а в смысле это я в строном доме живу
get dressed or just say come on
ты ты одеваешься или просто говоришь
you say and get dressed no I get dressed well
давай ты говори и одевайся нет я
wait yes put the phone down and get
одеваюсь ну подожди да положи телефон да
dressed Busya just wondering yes
оденься буся просто интересно
I've never seen yes how they live in
да я никогда не видел да как живут в
these He pressed something wrong
этих Нажал он что-то не
oh damn we won't find out what in the five-story building
то ай блин не узнаем мы что в пятиэтажке
Androni the
андрони
ruler made the dude in slippers
повелитель заставил чувака в тапочках
crawl around the rainy area at 4 in the morning there
лазить в 4 утра там по
show
району дождвому показывать
all the damn dudes took to your phone by
все блин чуваклы брал на цей телефон
clicking with your finger
нажав пальцем
sign up on Telegram directly
дапишись на Telegram прямо
Infectiously the axis of vin and
Зараз ось він а
priest is even more and more important youtube is
попик це дуже и дуже важливо youtube
banning us through kargerki into a shadow
заганяе нас через каргерки в тіньовий
ban and the video is not shown to
бан и дуже багато відео не показуется
people at all times information
людям вчасно не показуется інформація
about the stream is not shown in order for us to be
про стрими тому для того щоб ми мали
operational  Sign up to subscribe right
оперативный зв'язок підпишиться прямо
away and theres a pop there in the telegram where theres
зараз а попик там в телеграмі окмде ще
also some useful and useful information and were
теж є цікава и корисна інформація и мы
obliged to provide you with a permanent
повинні з вами тримати постійний
operational link regardless of the fact that well
оперативный зв'язок незалежно від того
show you about this YouTube Glory to
чи покаже вам про цей YouTube слава
Ukraine Subscribe
Україні підпишись